alphamedpress.org 2006-10-10

# AlphaMed Press -- Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

AlphaMed Press, publisher of **_Stem Cells_** , **_The Oncologist_** , and other related publications, is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide us when using any of the AlphaMed Press Web sites. We do not sell, exchange, or release any of your personal information.  

Third-party partners of AlphaMed Press and other Web sites that you may access via the AlphaMed Press Web site have different privacy policies and are not subject to this policy. We recommend that you read the privacy statement of each such Web site to find out how they protect your personal information.   

AlphaMed Press maintains this Web site in conjunction with Stanford University’s HighWire Press (see <http://highwire.stanford.edu/about/privacy.dtl>). Together we offer online services and access to the journals **_Stem Cells_** and **_The Oncologist_**.

 **Information We Collect**  
Information we collect may include your name, address (postal and e-mail), and telephone and fax numbers, as well as facts about your profession or other demographic information. If you request access to paid content, including subscriptions, we will also ask you for credit card payment information. 

**How We Use Information Collected**  
The information we collect may be used to: 

  * Process, validate, and fulfill orders or subscriptions to **_Stem Cells_** and **_The Oncologist_**. 
  * Process, validate, and fulfill orders for books published by AlphaMed Press. 
  * Improve the content and/or services of our Web site. 
  * Send notifications about new or existing products, content, or services. 
  * Report aggregate activity about our Web site to funders who have given us grants to support AlphaMed Press on the Web.

We **do not release** any information about your use of our site, including your e-mail address, to any third party. We **do not rent or sell** your e-mail address to any third party. 

**How to Stop Receiving Information from Us**  
You may choose at any time to stop receiving offer information from us about content or services. To stop receiving information, please contact:

Editorial Office  
e-mail: [EditorialOffice@AlphaMedPress.com](mailto:EditorialOffice@AlphaMedPress.com)  
318 Blackwell St., Suite 260  
Durham, NC 27701-2884 USA  
Telephone: 919-680-0011

Under normal conditions, you can expect your request to take 48–72 hours to be processed. 

**About the Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are small files that are created to store information on your computer. AlphaMed Press does not use cookies to track what other sites you have visited or to look at or track any personal or confidential information about you. Cookies are a required feature to support the personalization, registration, and sign-in features within AlphaMed Press Web sites. You may use our site without cookies if you choose not to register, sign in, or use personalization features. 

**Surveys**  
We may conduct occasional online surveys. These surveys are entirely voluntary, and you may easily decline to participate.

 **Policy Modification**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact the Editorial Office at [EditorialOffice@AlphaMedPress.com](mailto:EditorialOffice@AlphaMedPress.com).   
Last updated: December 23, 2005

 **REFUND/RETURN POLICY**

**Subscription Satisfaction Guarantee**  
If you are not happy with your subscription and wish to cancel, we will issue a full refund of your money. If there is an error in the processing of your subscription order, we will issue a refund to your credit card as soon as possible.

**Books**  
For book purchases, you may receive a full refund on the book purchase price within 30 days of delivery. You will be responsible for the return shipping costs. For returns, please contact:

Editorial Office  
e-mail: [EditorialOffice@AlphaMedPress.com](mailto:EditorialOffice@AlphaMedPress.com)  
318 Blackwell St., Suite 260  
Durham, NC 27701-2884 USA  
Telephone: 919-680-0011

* * *

**Copyright © 2006 by AlphaMed Press.**
